

# CONTACT

+1 508-641-8118

bowershaley3@gmail.com

github.com/bowershaley

## EDUCATION

#### **SheCodes**

Front End Developer Coding and Web Design 2023-2024

## **BFA** in Sound Design

Savannah College of Art and Design 2014-2018

## SKILLS & TOOLS

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- API
- · Visual Studio Code
- Bootstrap
- Responsive
- Github
- Netlify
- AI

# HALEY BOWERS

#### JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### PORTFOLIO

https://haleybowersportfolio.netlify.app/

#### ABOUT ME

Hello! My name is Haley. I received my BFA in Sound Design for TV and Film. I worked in marketing but did not feel fulfilled. I decided to seek a new path and after research and practice, I chose coding. I am always on the road and love to work from coffee shops. I also edit podcasts!

#### EXPERIENCE

## **SheCodes**

Front End Developer Graduate

Dec 2023 - March 2024

- Learned coding and web design
- Exposure to multiple programs and professional workflows
- Design, build, and debug websites

#### **Freelance Creative Services**

Self-Employed

2018 - Current

- Edits audio for podcasts, commercials, short film, etc.
- Graphic design and photoshop retouching
- Content creation from videos/audio for social media

## **Creative Project Manager**

Validated Insights

Dec 2021 - Oct 2023

- Managed static and video campaigns for multiple clients in higher education
- Communicated with clients on campaign performance on social media
- Planned and prepared advertising and promotional material to increase sales of products or services